{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Derived units are obtained from various combinations of", "opta": "electrical quantities", "optb": "fundamental units", "optc": "metric prefixes", "optd": "international standards", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following metric prefixes could replace 10\u20139?", "opta": "Nano", "optb": "Mega", "optc": "Kilo", "optd": "Micro", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Scientific notation is a method", "opta": "of expressing a very large number", "optb": "of expressing a very small number", "optc": "used to make calculations with large and small numbers", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If you drop a 5 when rounding a number, you are using the", "opta": "round-to-even rule", "optb": "significant digit rule", "optc": "round-off rule", "optd": "retained digit rule", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "7200 mV is the same as", "opta": "7.2 V", "optb": "7.2 V", "optc": "7,200,000 V", "optd": "0.0072 V", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A measure of the repeatability of a measurement of some quantity is", "opta": "error", "optb": "precision", "optc": "accuracy", "optd": "significant", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Another name for \"fundamental units\" is", "opta": "base units", "optb": "atoms", "optc": "the metric system", "optd": "letter symbols", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Adding 27.5 \u00d7 103 to 8.9 \u00d7 104 equals", "opta": "36.4 \u00d7 107", "optb": "116.5 \u00d7 104", "optc": "28.39 \u00d7 103", "optd": "1.165 \u00d7 105", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using the terms \"accuracy\" and \"precision\" for measurements", "opta": "\"precision\" implies less measurement error than \"accuracy\"", "optb": "\"accuracy\" implies less measurement error than \"precision\"", "optc": "\"precision\" measures the repeatability of a measurement", "optd": "both terms mean the same thing", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The difference between scientific and engineering notation is", "opta": "powers of ten representation", "optb": "single vs. multiple digits before decimal point", "optc": "groupings of multiples of three digits", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The number 14.8 can also be expressed as", "opta": "1.48 \u00d7 10\u20131", "optb": "1.48 \u00d7 100", "optc": "1.48 \u00d7 101", "optd": "1.48 \u00d7 102", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The digits in a measured number that are known to be correct are called", "opta": "accuracy digits", "optb": "significant digits", "optc": "error digits", "optd": "precision digits", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is expressed in engineering notation?", "opta": "470 \u00d7 105", "optb": "82 \u00d7 10\u20132", "optc": "9.1 \u00d7 10\u20136", "optd": "14.7 \u00d7 108", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The unit for frequency is the", "opta": "hertz", "optb": "ampere", "optc": "watt", "optd": "second", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Add 21 mA and 8000 A and express the result in milliamperes.", "opta": "21.8 mA", "optb": "218 mA", "optc": "29 mA", "optd": "290 mA", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Dividing 24 \u00d7 1011 by 3 \u00d7 104 equals", "opta": "8 \u00d7 104", "optb": "8 \u00d7 107", "optc": "8 \u00d7 1011", "optd": "8 \u00d7 1015", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Pico is what relation to micro?", "opta": "one-tenth", "optb": "one-hundredth", "optc": "one-thousandth", "optd": "one-millionth", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}